When terrorists strike, Trident Force strikes back... TWICE AS HARD!
The Trident Force is a action film directed by Richard Smith.
An outbreak of bombings, assassinations, and massacres by an extremist, Marxist terrorist group, alarms
the international community who calls for help - the ultimate solution - the Trident Force.
Rashid, played by Anthony Alonzo.
Lesley Prentiss, played by Nanna Anderson.
Ahmed, played by Mark Gil.
Hawthorn, played by Steve Rogers.
Abu Hassad (as Ed Gaerlan), played by Eddie Gaerlan.
Casey, played by Ronnie Patterson.
Trident Force (also known as The Ultimate Solution) is a 1988 Filipino action film directed by Richard
Smith and starring Anthony Alonzo, Nanna Anderson, Mark Gil, Steve Rogers, Eddie M.
Gaerlan, Ronnie Patterson, Nick Nicholson, and Willy Schober.
Produced by ANNA Films International, the film was released by
Solar Films in the Philippines on December 16, 1988.
Critic Lav Diaz gave Trident Force a mixed review, deeming its competent filmmaking to
be undermined by stereotypical villains and exaggerated characters.